creationwatches.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy :

**Privacy Information**

Data protection policy information of **Redsol Pte Ltd., Owner of The Website ([http://www.creationwatches.com](http://www.creationwatches.com/))**

1.0 Redsol Pte Ltd. explains how we process data, it’s legal bases and pursuit of legitimate business interests by the Redsol Pte Ltd. or associate third party as well as categories of recipients.

**1.1. Calling our websites / applications**

**1.1.1. Cookies, Log-Files, tracking, social media plugins**

Whenever you access our website, data is transmitted over the internet to our web server(s). This happens via Internet browser of the device you use. The data so collected is stored in temporarily log files. These log files contain the following data and are stored until they are automatically deleted; date and time of retrieval of information, name of the webpage requested, referrer URL (in case you arrived via a link), IP address of the requesting device, load time, volume of data transferred and ancillary information i.e. browser version and name of internet service provider. Redsol Pte Ltd. makes use of ‘cookies’, tracking tools and targeting methods and social media plug-ins. To collect this data, a cookie may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Services. Cookies contain a small amount of information that allows our web servers to recognize you. We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or clear gifs to record your preferences. We may also automatically collect information about your use of features of our Services, about the functionality of our Services, frequency of visits, and other information related to your interactions with the Services.

Redsol Pte Ltd. can legally obtain and process the IP address as mandated in Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR. We require this information to:  
• Ensuring comfortable user-interface for our website and or application (or both),  
• Ensuring a smooth transfer of data,  
• Ensuring data security.

We would like to confirm that with the above information, we can neither directly establish your identity, nor infer other personal details.

All such data collected is automatically deleted when it is no longer required.

**1.2. Justification, implementation and / or termination of a contract**

**1.2.1. Data processing on conclusion of the contract**

If you register with Redsol Pte Ltd. or one of our Apps, or buy a product from our website, we will process the data necessary to successfully conclude the transaction. This includes:  
• Full name  
• Billing address  
• Delivery address  
• E-mail address  
• Billing and payment data  
• Telephone number

The legal basis for collecting the above information is Article 6 (1) (a) and (b) GDPR.

So long as we do not use your data for advertising purposes (see below 1.3.), 1e store the data collected for the execution of the purchase. The duration of such storage is dictated by necessity e.g. statutory or potential contractual warranty and guarantee rights.

Furthermore, after expiry of above period, information is retained to fulfil our legal obligation to the commercial and tax laws.

To process a purchase a product via our websites / app, the following additional data processing is required:

Your payment data will be encrypted and securely passed on to our payment service providers for processing of your payment. Information such as your delivery address, email and telephone number is passed on to our logistics and shipping partners so that they can send you (and us) intimation once the product is shipped and expected date of delivery.

The logistics partner(s) may contact you to ascertain suitable time of delivery.

**1.2.2. Creditworthiness and transmission to credit bureaus**

Redsol Pte Ltd. generally grants its customers the option of purchasing goods using insecure payment methods.

Generally speaking, there are two types of payment mechanism offered:  
Secure, online and,  
Non-secure offline

To protect our business interests, Redsol Pte Ltd. might in certain instances, check the creditworthiness of its customer before granting the option of using insecure payment methods.

Within this framework, Redsol Pte Ltd. is entitled to use negative credit information, which it has collected for the respective customer. Furthermore, Redsol Pte Ltd. is entitled to provide negative credit information about the respective customer to the other business associates of Redsol Pte Ltd. This is done in order to minimize the prospect of losses on account of fraud.

In cases where a customer opts to use insecure means of payment, Redsol Pte Ltd. is entitled to use credit information obtained in the order to calculate probability of non-payment and fraud. This calculation is done via internal scoring and is based on a recognized mathematical statistical procedure. In particular, the data used in internal scoring results from a combination of the following data categories: address data, age, desired payment terms, order path, and assortment groups. As part of the internal scoring, only such data are used, which the customer has indicated to us. As part of the examination of whether an insecure payment method can be granted, we are also entitled to obtain credit information about you from an external credit agency. For the purpose of soliciting credit information, the following information is transmitted to the external credit reporting agency: first name, last name, postal address, date of birth.

As part of the credit check, we can decide by means of an automated process whether you are granted the desired insecure payment method (instalment / invoice payment). For example, when submitting a negative credit report by an information agency or when calculating an insufficient score within the scope of the internal scoring, a rejection of the desired payment method can be carried out automatically. You can assert the right for us to make a manual review of the automated decision. In addition, you have the right to make your own views and to challenge the decision.

The processing of your data as part of the credit check is carried out on the basis of Article 6 (1) (b) DSGVO and Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR. In principle, we have a legitimate interest in the execution of a credit check when selecting an insecure payment method (instalment / invoice purchase) by you.

**1.2.3. Use of data for fraud prevention purposes**

The information you provide in the context of an order can be used to verify that there is an atypical ordering process (for example, simultaneous ordering of a large number of goods to the same address using different customer accounts). In principle, there is a legitimate interest in the performance of such a review. The legal basis of the processing is Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

**1.2.4. Transmission of data to transport**

Service providers for the purpose of delivering ordered goods, we work together with logistics service providers / transport companies and / or shipping partners: to these the following data may be transmitted for the purpose of delivering the ordered goods or for their announcement: first name, last name, postal address, E-mail address, telephone number (e.g. for forwarding announcements). The legal basis of the processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR.

**1.2.5. Transmission of data on outstanding claims to collection service providers**

If you fail to settle outstanding invoices / instalments despite a repeated reminder, we may forward the data required for the performance of collection to a debt collection agency for the purpose of fiduciary collection. Alternatively, we can sell the outstanding claims to a debt collection agency. He then becomes the debtor and claims in his own name. Redsol Pte Ltd. may cooperate with contracted debt collection service provider. The legal basis for the transfer of data in the context of fiduciary collection is Article 6 (1) (b) GDPR; the transmission of data in connection with the sale of receivables is based on Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

**1.2.6. Transmission of data to partner companies**

You have the opportunity to use third-party offers on our platform. In these cases, you may conclude a contract directly with our partner to whom the data required for the performance of the contract (eg first name, last name, billing and delivery address, e-mail address, billing and payment data, date of birth, telephone number) are transmitted. Such advantages offered by our partners are recognizable as partner offers. The legal basis for this data processing is Article 6 (1) (b), (f) GDPR.

**1.2.6.2. Items from other sellers**

In order to offer our customers an even larger and more attractive selection, Redsol Pte Ltd. cooperates with selected partners who offer their products and services on their own behalf and for their own account at Redsol Pte Ltd. online portal.

If you order a partner article, a contract may only be concluded between you and the partner. When ordering such an article the general terms and conditions and possibly the privacy policy of the partner apply. The general terms and conditions and privacy policy of the partner may in individual cases deviate from the general terms and conditions of Redsol Pte Ltd. . By sending your order or - for example, in the case of processing special categories of personal data (Article 9 GDPR) by express consent - you accept the privacy policy of the partner. In this case, Redsol Pte Ltd. is not your contractual partner and, with regard to the processing of the data by the partner, is not responsible for the data protection law.

If you order several articles from different partners and Redsol Pte Ltd. , the respective terms and conditions and privacy policy of each seller apply to each article. Your data necessary for the transaction (first name, name, address, date of birth, telephone number and e-mail address) will be stored by Redsol Pte Ltd. and passed on to our partner for their own fulfilment of the contract. This may use your e-mail address for sending information about your order.

**1.3. Data processing for advertising purposes**

**1.3.1. Advertising**

We have a legitimate interest in using your information for marketing purposes. We use the following data for our own marketing and third-party marketing purposes: first name, last name, postal address, year of birth.

In addition, we are entitled to store additional personal data about you in compliance with legal requirements for your own marketing purposes as well as for the marketing purposes of third parties. The aim is to provide you with advertisements oriented solely to your actual or perceived needs, and not to bother you with useless advertising.

A transmission of the added data to third parties does not take place. In addition, Redsol Pte Ltd. pseudonymizes / anonymizes personal data collected about you for the purpose of using the pseudonymized / anonymized data for its own marketing purposes as well as for marketing purposes of third parties (advertisers).

The pseudonymized / anonymized data can also be used to advertise online individualized, whereby the control of advertising by third party service providers and / or agencies can be done. The legal basis for the use of personal data for marketing purposes is Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

Reference to the right of opposition

You can object to the use of your personal data for the aforementioned marketing purposes at any time free of charge with effect for the future at contact@creationwatches.com

Insofar as you object, your data will be blocked for further processing.

**1.3.2. Newsletter**

On our websites / applications we offer you the opportunity to subscribe to our newsletter through the sign-up box. In order to be sure that no errors have occurred when entering the email address, we use the so-called double-opt-in procedure (DOI procedure): After you have entered your email address in the registration field and given your consent to Receipt of our newsletter, we will send you a confirmation link to the specified address. Only when you click this confirmation link, your email address will be included in our mailing list to send our newsletter. The legal basis for this data processing is Article 6 (1) (a) GDPR.

If you opt to receive our newsletter during the checkout process, we will include you in our mailing list. There is no double-opt-in in this case.

Notice of withdrawal

You can revoke your consent at any time with effect for the future by sending a message to contact@creationwatches.com or by opting out at the end of each newsletter.

**1.4. Online appearance and website optimization**

**1.4.1. Cookies - General Information**

We use cookies on various pages in order to make the visit to our website attractive and to enable the use of certain functions and to statistically record the use of our website. Cookies are small text files that your browser automatically creates and that are stored on your device (laptop, tablet, smartphone, etc.) when you visit our site. Cookies do not harm your device, do not contain viruses, Trojans or other malicious software. In the cookie information is stored, each resulting in connection with the specific terminal used. However, this does not mean that we are immediately aware of your identity.

Most of the cookies we use are deleted after the end of the browser session (so-called session or session cookies). Through this we can offer you e.g. the cross-page shopping cart, where you can read off how many items are currently in your shopping cart and how high your current purchase value is. Other cookies remain on your computer and allow us to recognize your computer the next time you visit (so-called permanent or cross-session cookies). In particular, these cookies serve to make our offer user-friendly, effective and secure. For example, these files may allow you to see information that is specifically tailored to your interests on the page.

Of course, you can set up your browser so that it does not store our cookies on your device. The Help menu on the menu bar of most web browsers tells you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to let your browser know when you receive a new cookie, or how to delete all cookies you have already received and for all others can lock.

Please proceed as follows:

In Internet Explorer:  
1\. From the "Tools" menu, select "Internet Options".  
2\. Click on the "Privacy" tab.  
3\. Now you can set the security settings for the Internet zone. Here you can set whether and which cookies should be accepted or rejected.  
4\. Confirm your setting with "OK".

In Firefox:  
1\. From the Tools menu, select Settings.  
2\. Click "Privacy".  
3\. In the drop-down menu, select "Create custom settings".  
4\. Now you can set whether to accept cookies, how long you want to keep these cookies and add exceptions to which websites you always or never want to allow cookies to use.  
5\. Confirm your setting with "OK".

In Google Chrome:  
1\. Click the Chrome menu in the browser toolbar.  
2\. Now select "Settings".  
3\. Click on "Show advanced settings".  
4\. Under "Privacy," click "Content Settings."  
5\. Under "Cookies" you can configure the following settings for cookies:

• Delete cookies  
• Block cookies by default • Delete  
Cookies and website data by default after quitting the browser  
• Allow exceptions for cookies from certain websites or domains

The data collection and storage can be deactivated at any time with future effect in this browser here.

We point out, however, that in this case you may not be able to use all the functions of this website in full.

Insofar as these cookies and / or information contained therein are personal data, the legal basis of data processing is Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR. Our interest in optimizing our website is considered to be justified in the sense of the aforementioned provision.

**1.4.2. Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (" Google "), for the purpose of designing and continuously optimizing our websites in accordance with Article 6 paragraph 1 (f) GDPR. Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website by you. In this context, pseudonymised usage profiles are created and cookies are used. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website such as  
• Browser type / version,  
• Used operating system,  
• Referrer URL (the previously visited page),  
• Host name of the accessing computer (IP address),  
• Time of the server request

On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services related to website activity and internet usage to the website operator. The IP address provided by Google Analytics as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with other Google data. You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software; however, please note that in this case you may not be able to use all the features of this website to the full extent. You may also collect the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website You can opt out of google analytics tracking from here - <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

**1.4.4. Google AdWords**

Our website uses the Google AdWords service. Google AdWords is an online advertising program provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google").

On the one hand we use the remarketing function within the Google AdWords service. The Remarketing feature allows us to show users of our website on other sites within the Google Display Network (on Google itself, so-called "Google Ads" or other websites) advertising based on their interests. For this, the interaction of users on our website is analysed, e.g. which offers the user was interested in, in order to be able to display targeted advertising to users even after visiting our website on other sites. Google stores a number in the browsers of users who visit certain Google services or websites on the Google Display Network. This number, referred to as a "cookie", records the visits of these users. This number is used to uniquely identify a web browser on a particular computer and not to identify a person; personal information will not be stored. The legal basis for this data processing is Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

You may disable the use of cookies by Google by following the link below and downloading and installing the plug-in provided there: [www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin)

For more information about Google Remarketing and Google's privacy policy, please visit: [www.google.com/privacy/ads/](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)

**1.4.5. Google Conversion Tracking**

We also use so-called conversion tracking when using the Google AdWords service. When you click on an ad served by Google, a conversion tracking cookie will be placed on your computer / device. These cookies lose their validity after 30 days, contain no personal data and are thus not used for personal identification. The information gathered using the conversion cookie is used to generate conversion statistics for AdWords advertisers who have opted for conversion tracking.

The legal basis for this data processing is Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software; however, please note that in this case you may not be able to use all the features of this website to the full extent. In addition, you can opt-out of interest-based ads on Google and interest-based Google ads on the web (within the Google Display Network) in your browser by turning off or turning off <http://www.google.com/settings/ads> at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> . For more information about your preferences and privacy on Google, please visit: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/?fg=1>

**1.4.7. Targeting**

The so-called targeting measures listed below and used by us are implemented on the basis of Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR. We use the targeting measures that we use to ensure that only advertisements that are based on your actual or supposedly interests-oriented advertising are displayed on your end devices and that you are not bothered with advertisements that are of no interest to you.

**1.4.8.1. Onsite Targeting**

Our website uses cookie information to collect and evaluate ad serving optimization information. For example, this information may contain information about which products you have viewed on our websites / applications. The collection and evaluation is done exclusively pseudonym and does not allow us to identify you. In particular, the information will not be matched with personally identifiable information about you. On the basis of the information, we can show you on our site offers that are specifically geared to your interests, as they result from your previous user behaviour.

**1.4.8.2. Retargeting**

We also use retargeting technologies from external service providers, such as the Pixel of Facebook Ireland Limited. Retargeting allows us to make our online offer more interesting to you. In this way, we can specifically target those users of online advertising who have already taken an interest in our shop and our products on the websites of our partners. From studies we know that the display of personalized, interest-based advertising for the Internet user is more interesting than advertising, which has no such personal reference.

For this purpose, a cookie is set, with which interest data are collected using pseudonyms. On the basis of this information, you will be shown interest-based advertisements for our offers on the websites of our partners. No personally identifiable information will be stored and no user profiles will be merged with personally identifiable information about you.

You have the option to enable or disable the collection of data for the purpose of personalized advertising. A cookie will then be set that permanently prevents the collection of data, unless you select this cookie in your browser or delete it using the "Delete all cookies" function. The contradiction can be repeated at any time.

**1.4.9. Advertising partners / third party cookies**

We work with advertising partners to make the online offer on our site even more interesting to you. For this purpose, cookies are set by our advertising partners when visiting our site (so-called third-party cookies). In the cookies of our advertising partners information is also stored using pseudonyms about your user behaviour and your interests when visiting our site. Partly also information is recorded, which resulted before the visit of our side on other sides. This information will be used to show you interest-based advertisements of our advertising partners. No personal data will be stored and no user profiles will be merged with personal data.

You can prevent the interest-based advertising of our advertising partners by a corresponding cookie setting in your browser.

**1.4.10. Opposition / opt-out option**

In addition to the deactivation methods already described, you can generally prevent the described technologies by setting a corresponding cookie in your browser. In addition, you have the option of deactivating preference-based advertising with the help of the preference manager available here.

**1.5. Social media plug-ins**

We use social plug-ins from Facebook, Google+ and Twitter on our website based on Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR to make our company better known. The underlying commercial purpose is to be regarded as a legitimate interest within the meaning of the GDPR. Responsibility for the operation compliant with data protection is to be guaranteed by their respective providers.

The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by the respective provider, as well as your related rights and settings options for the protection of your privacy, please refer to the respective privacy policy of the provider, which we link in the following.

By logging out of social media sites and deleting cookies, you can prevent social networks from associating your collected information with your social network user account during your visit to our website. If you do not want social networks to directly associate the data collected via our website with your profile, you must log out of the relevant social networks before visiting our website.

**1.5.1. Facebook, Google+ and YouTube**

This website uses social plug-ins from Facebook and Google (Google+ and YouTube). These are offers from the US companies Facebook and Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google")).

If you visit a page that contains such a plugin, your browser will connect to Facebook or Google and the content will be loaded from these pages. Your visit to this site may be tracked by Facebook and Google, even if you are not actively using the Social Plugin feature. If you have an account on Facebook or Google, you can use such a social plugin and share information with your friends. Redsol Pte Ltd. has no influence on the content of the plugins and the transmission of information.

On their websites, Facebook and Google provide detailed information on the scope, nature, purpose and processing of your data. Here you will also find further information about your rights and settings options for protecting your privacy.

Facebook Privacy Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy>

Google Privacy Policy: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy>

**1.5.2. Pinterest**

This site incorporates plugins from Pinterest Inc., 635 High Street, Palo Alto, CA, 94301, USA ("Pinterest"). The Pinterest Plugin can be recognized by the "Pin it Button" on our site.

If you click on the Pinterest "Pin it button" while logged in to your Pinterest account, you can link the contents of our pages to your Pinterest profile. This allows Pinterest to associate your visit to our pages with your user account. We point out that we are not aware of the content of the transmitted data and their use by Pinterest. For more information, see the privacy policy of Pinterest: <https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy>

**1.5.3. Twitter**

This website also includes features of the Twitter service. These features are provided by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA ("Twitter"). By using Twitter and the "Re-Tweet" function, the websites you visit are linked to your Twitter account and shared with other users. This data is also transmitted to Twitter. Your Internet browser makes a direct connection to the servers of Twitter and transmits data to Twitter.

We point out that we are not aware of the content of the transmitted data and their use by Twitter. For more information, see the privacy policy of Twitter: <https://twitter.com/privacy>

You can change your privacy settings on Twitter in the Account Settings <https://twitter.com/account/settings>

**1.5.4. Instagram**

This site also integrates plugins from Instagram Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA, 94025, USA ("Instagram"). The Instagram plugin can be recognized by the "Instagram button" on our page.

If you click on the "Instagram Button" while logged into your Instagram account, you can link the contents of our pages to your Instagram profile. This allows Instagram to associate your visit to our pages with your user account. Please note that we are not aware of the content of the submitted data and their use by Instagram. For more information, see the Instagram Privacy Policy: <https://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy>

**1.5.5. WhatsApp**

This site may also use a WhatsApp (WhatsApp Share Button) button. With this button you can share content from the Website via the WhatsApp application on your mobile phone. The button is a hyperlink. When the button appears on this website, no personal data is transmitted to the operator of WhatsApp or other third parties. Once you use the WhatsApp button, the WhatsApp operator will learn what content is shared and that the button has been used on this website. For more information on the handling of personal data by the WhatsApp operator, see the operator's privacy policy: <https://www.whatsapp.com/legal/#Privacy>

**1.6. Customer account / user account**

Registration on the Website is not required. Customers can shop without registering or creating an account explicitly. You have the option to delete your customer data stored with us at any time by emailing contact@creationwatches.com. Please note, however, that this does not mean that the data can be deleted once you have requested us. The deletion of your data takes place automatically after the expiry of our commercial and tax-related retention obligations. The legal basis for this further data processing is Article 6 (1) (c) GDPR and Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

**1.7. Contact**

You have the opportunity to contact us in several ways. By e-mail, by phone, by chat or by post. When you contact us, we will use the personal information you provide to us voluntarily for the sole purpose of contacting you and processing your request.

The legal basis for this data processing is Article 6 (1) (a), Article 6 (1) (b), Article 6 (1) (c) GDPR and Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

**1.8. Customer**

Reviews / Comments - If users leave comments or other posts on the Website, their IP addresses will be based on our legitimate interests within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 letter f). DSGVO stored for 7 or 14 days. This is for our own safety, if someone leaves illegal content in comments and contributions (insults, prohibited political propaganda, etc.).

**1.9. Other contents of users**

You have the opportunity to publish your own content on the Website at various points (e.g. product reviews, comments, etc.). When you submit a comment, recommendation, or review on products, brands, and styles, we process any personal information that you voluntarily enter in the comments or ratings. You can edit content at the Website publish under a pseudonym and / or your first name and shortened surname.

The legal basis for this data processing (s) is Article 6 (1) (a), Article 6 (1) (b) and Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR. In addition, our terms of use, which you can access here, apply to your own content settings on.

**1.10 Payments**

We process your payment information for the purpose of payment processing, eg if you purchase or use a product and / or service via the Website. Depending on the method of payment, we will forward your payment information to third parties (eg credit card payments to your credit card provider).

The legal basis for this data processing is Article 6 (1) (a), Article 6 (1) (b), DSGVO and Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

**1.10.1. PayPal**

When paying via PayPal, your payment details will be forwarded to Paypal. PayPal reserves itself for the payment methods credit card via PayPal, direct debit via PayPal or - if offered - "purchase on account" via PayPal the execution of a credit check. The result of the credit check on the statistical probability of default is used by PayPal for the purpose of deciding on the provision of the respective payment method. The credit report may contain probability values (so-called score values). As far as score values are included in the result of the credit report. These have their basis in a scientifically recognized mathematical-statistical process. The calculation of score values includes, among other things, address data. Further data protection information, among other things to the used credit agencies, please refer to the privacy policy of PayPal:

<https://www.paypal.com/sg/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

**1.10.4 Your rights**

**1.10.5.1. Overview**

In addition to the right of revocation of your consent granted to us, the following further rights are available to you if the respective legal requirements apply:  
• The right to information about your personal data stored by us (Article 15 GDPR) , in particular you can provide information about the processing purposes, the category of personal data, the categories of recipients to whom your data has been disclosed, the planned storage period the origin of their data, if they were not collected directly from you;  
• The right to correct inaccurate or correct data (Art. 16 GDPR),  
• The right to delete your stored data (article 17 GDPR), as far as no legal or contractual retention periods or other legal obligations or rights for further storage of us must be observed,  
• The right to limit the processing of your data (Art. 18 GDPR), as far as the accuracy of the data is disputed by you. If you purchase via the Website products / services from partners, the aforementioned rights apply to our partners accordingly. If you wish to assert the aforementioned rights towards our partners, simply contact the respective partner directly.  
• The right to data portability acc. Art. 20 DSGVO, i.e the right to transfer selected data stored in a standard, machine-readable format, or to request transmission to another person responsible.  
• The right to complain to a supervisory authority.

You can assert the above-mentioned rights which you have towards us under contact@creationwatches.com .You can assert the right to data portability in your customer account.

If you purchase products / services from partners via the Website, the aforementioned rights apply to our partners accordingly. If you want to assert the aforementioned rights towards our partners, simply contact the respective partner directly.

You can also request information about your personal data stored.

**1.10.5.3. Right of objection**

Under the conditions of Article 21 (1) GDPR, data processing can be objected to for reasons that arise from the particular situation of the data subject.

The above general right of objection applies to all processing purposes described in this privacy statement, which are processed on the basis of Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR. Unlike the special right of objection to data processing for advertising purposes, according to the GDPR we are only obliged to implement such a general objection if you give us reasons of overriding importance (e.g. a possible danger to life or health).

**1.10.5.4 Right of Withdrawal**

In so far as we process data on the basis of your consent, you have the right at any time to revoke your consent. The revocation of the consent does not mean that the data processing carried out on the basis of the consent until the time of the revocation becomes ineffective.

**1.10.6. Data security**

All personal data transmitted, including your payment data, are transmitted using the generally accepted and secure standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer). SSL is a secure and proven standard that is also used in online banking. You will see a secure SSL connection, including the attached s at the http (ie https: // ...) in the address bar of your browser or the lock icon at the bottom of your browser.

Incidentally, we use appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal data stored against us against manipulation, partial or complete loss and against unauthorized access by third parties. Our security measures are continuously improved in line with technological developments.

**1.10.6.1. Spoofing, spam and phishing warnings**

The security of our customers' data is our top priority. Below we would like to give you some safety instructions.

Beware of so-called phishing and spoofing attempts.

In this scam mesh, unfortunately, the brand Redsol Pte Ltd. is misused as a supposed sender. Specifically, this means that consumers receive fake emails on behalf of Redsol Pte Ltd. . These e-mails are often based on the Redsol Pte Ltd. brand layout and may be difficult to distinguish from genuine e-mails from Redsol Pte Ltd.

The fraudsters want to exploit the trust between Redsol Pte Ltd. and our customers and thereby steal sensitive data (e.g. login, customer information, payment information) or install malicious software (such as viruses or Trojans) on your computer or smartphone.

The creation of these e-mails and the shipping will not be done by Redsol Pte Ltd. , even if our name should be used as sender. Unfortunately, Redsol Pte Ltd. cannot influence the sending of these illegal e-mails.

Here are some features that help you recognize emails from Redsol Pte Ltd.:  
• Redsol Pte Ltd. does not ask you for personal information by e-mail, nor does Redsol Pte Ltd. ask you for confirmation of personal information via a link in an e-mail.  
• You will receive order confirmations and invoices from Redsol Pte Ltd. only for orders that you have actually made.  
• Redsol Pte Ltd. only sends e-mails with file attachments if you have requested them explicitly from us (eg operating instructions).  
• Mails from Redsol Pte Ltd. should have no spelling and grammatical errors, as they are always proofread before shipping.  

How to properly handle spam, phishing and spoofing emails:  
• We recommend that you delete suspicious emails immediately.  
• Never open links and attachments in suspicious emails or disclose personal information.

Our tip and service for you: If you are ever unsure, just send us an e-mail to: contact@creationwatches.com

**1.10.6.2. Important Notes on Protecting Your Data**

In today's connected world, unauthorized access to personally identifiable information is a reality that individuals and businesses face every day. That's a big challenge without question.

Since privacy is our highest priority, we invest in the security of our systems and constantly monitor them. Because when you buy online at the Website you entrust us with information about yourself. The security of this information is important to us. Since you too can do something to protect against the unauthorized access of third parties to your information, we would like to give you some advice on how to handle your information safely.

**How can I protect my personal information?**

Basically: Protect your customer account and also your computer, laptop or your mobile device with secure passwords and PIN codes that only you know.

**Are there any other things I should consider?**

If you ever use a publicly accessible computer, always make sure that you log out after your visit to the Website.

If you receive unsolicited e-mails without concrete contact, asking you to provide the Website passwords or giving details of payment details, please ignore this and contact us immediately at contact@creationwatches.com. We will investigate these incidents.
